question_data = [
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "Amazon acquired Twitch in August 2014 for $970 million dollars.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},

    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "The vapor produced by e-cigarettes is actually water.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},

    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Mythology",
     "question": "The Roman god Jupiter was first known as Zeus to the Greeks.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},

    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Geography",
     "question": "There exists an island named Java.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},

    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "History",
     "question": "Brezhnev was the 5th leader of the USSR.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},

    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Animals",
     "question": "Finnish Lapphund dogs were used for herding reindeer.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},

    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "Popcorn was invented in 1871 by Frederick W. Rueckheim in the USA where he sold "
                 "the snack on the streets of Chicago.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},

    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "Kraft Cheez Whiz contains cheese culture, but doesn't actually contain cheese",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},

    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
     "question": "In Full Metal Panic!, Whispered are those who are capable of creating Black Technology.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},

    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "In Call Of Duty: Zombies, you can upgrade the Apothicon Servant in the Shadows Of Evil map.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}
]
